A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1974-2006.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction (Accession 39607), 1974-2006., Extent: xx boxes. (Box 1-xx)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. S. John Davis), 1979-1980.
    - Anthony Seeger Campus School Study Committee, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Administrative review, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Federal programs, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Boyer, Dr. R.L., 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Vocational Education Civil Rights Survey (School Census), 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Management Information Service, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Testing, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Howerton, Dr. E.B., 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Teacher Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Technical Assistance, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Community Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Shingleton, Dr. Callie, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Riehm, Dr. Carl L., 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Sciences and Elementary Administration, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Driver Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Health and Physical Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Mathematics Service, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Proprietary Schools, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Science Service, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Humanities and Secondary Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - English / Language Arts Service, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - History, Government, Geography, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Foreign Language, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Tubbs, Dr. N. Grant, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Special Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Booher, Dr. William, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Bureau of Teaching Materials, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Film Production, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Gifted and Talented, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Guidance, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - School libraries and texbooks, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Telecommunications, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Title I, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Migrant Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Vocational Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Adult Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Agricultural Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Distributive Education, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Home Economics, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Veterans Training, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Sandidge, F.B., 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Basic school aid, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Personnel, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Monday, Dr. A., 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Finance, Dir. of, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Pupil transportation, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - School buildings, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - School food, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Public information, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - Summary reports - Board of Education meetings, 1979-1980. (Box 11b)
    - State Government: Appropriations Committee, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Attorney General, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Attorney General - Opinions, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Children, Division of, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Civil Digest, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Consumer Affairs (Dept. of Agriculture and Commerce), 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Comptroller's Office, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Conservation and Economice Development, Dept. of, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Emergency and Energy Services, Dept. of, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: General Services, Dept. of - Purchases and Supply, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Governor's Office, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Executive orders, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Memoranda, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Health Dept., 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Highways Dept., 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Intergovernmental Affairs, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Justice, Division of and Crime Commission, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: legislative Services, Division of, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Lieutenant Governor, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Management Analysis and Systems Development, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of; Mental Hygiene and Hospitals, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Miscellaneous State Agencies, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Rehabilitative School Authority, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: State Agency Group Luncheon, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Transportation and Safety, Dept. of, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Secretary of Administration, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education - Issue Identification, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education - Meeting with Dr. Gilley and Secretaries on Handicapped, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
    - State Government: Secretary of Human Affairs, 1979-1980. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. S. John Davis), 1981-1982.
    - A - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Applicants, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - American Association of School Administrators (AASA), 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Adult and Post High School Education, Study of, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Advisory Committees or Councils (Dept. of Education), 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Advisory Research Committee on Plans and Specifications for School Buildinds, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Annual Conference of Division Superintendents, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Appalachia Educational Laboratory, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Accomack County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Albemarle County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Alexandria City, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Alleghany County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Amelia County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Amherst County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Appomattox County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Arlington County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Augusta County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - B- Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Blood drive, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Bath County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Bedford County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Bland County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Bristol City, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Brunswick County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Buchanan County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Buckingham County, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Buena Vista, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - C - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Career Education, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Centex - Center for Excellence, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Central Office staff meetings, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Certificates of Appointment, 1981 July. (Box 13a)
    - Christmas Pary, 1981 Dec. (Box 13a)
    - Coleman, Marshall (for Governor), 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - CSR - Introduction and Elementary/Secondary Education (Dr. Perry Johnston), 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Colleges and Universities - Out of State, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Consolidation of Alleghany and Clifton Forge, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Copy Machines, Study of, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Council of Higher Education, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Council of Higher Education and Board of Education - Liaison Committee, 1981-1982. (Box 13a)
    - Campbell County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Cape Charles, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Caroline County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Carroll County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Charles City County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Charlottesville, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Chesapeake, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Chesterfield County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Chesterfield County - Lewis, W.E., 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Clarke County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Clifton Forge, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Colonial Beach, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Covington, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Craig County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Culpeper County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - D - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Developmental Disabilities Protection and Advocacy Office, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Danville, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Dickenson County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Dinwiddie County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - E - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Education Commission of the States, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Essex County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - F - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Federal audit requirements, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Fairfax County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Falls Church, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Fauquier County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Floyd County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Fluvanna County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Franklin City, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Franklin County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Frederick County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Fredericksburg, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Fries, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - G - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - General Assembly - House of Delegates, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - General Assembly - Other states, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - General Assembly - Senate of Virginia, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Great American Achievements Program, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Galax, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Gloucester County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Goochland County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Grayson County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Greene County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - Greensville County, 1981-1982. (Box 13b)
    - H - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Halifax County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Hampton, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Hanover County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Harrisonburg, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Henrico County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Highland County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Hopewell, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - I - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Isle of Wight County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - J - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Jobs for Virginia Graduates, Inc., 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Jointly owned vocational schools, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - K - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Keep America Beautiful, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - King and Queen County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - King George County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - King William County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - King William County - Educating Indian children, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - L - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Liaison Committee - Board of Education / Council of Higher Education, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Liberty Baptist College, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Lee County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Lexington, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Loudoun County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Louisa County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Lunenburg County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Lynchburg, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - M - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Marsh and McLennan (Liability Insurance), 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Madison County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Manassas, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Manassas Park, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Martinsville, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Mathews County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Mecklenburg County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Middlesex County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Montogmery County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - N - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education (NASBE), 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - National Commission on Excellence in Education (U.S. Dept. of Education), 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - National Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - National Education Association, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - NOONS, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Nelson County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - New Kent County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Newport News, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Norfolk, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Northampton County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Nottoway County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - O - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - On Board, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Orange County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - P - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Peninsula Area Cooperative Educational Services, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Presidental Classroom for Young Americans, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Patrick County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Petersburg, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Poquoson, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Portsmouth, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Powhatan County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Prince Edward County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Prince George County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Prince William County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - Pulaski County, 1981-1982. (Box 14a)
    - R - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Register of Regulations, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Robb, Charles, for Governor, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Rappahannock County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Richmond City, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Richmond County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Roanoke City, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Roanoke County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Rockbridge County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Rockingham County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Russell County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - S - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Southeastern Cooperative Education Programs, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - State Advocacy Office for the Developmentally Disabled, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - State Depts. of Education - Other states, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - State-Ed (newsletter), 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - State Special Education Advisory Committee, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Superintendent's Advisory County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Superintendent's Study Groups, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Salem, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Scott County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Shenandoah County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Smyth County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Southampton County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Stafford County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Staunton, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Suffolk, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Surry County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Sussex County, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - T - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - Title I - Audit correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - U - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - U.S. Congress, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - U.S. Secretary of Education, 1981-1982. (Box 14b)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education - Office of Civil Rights, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education - Office of Special Education, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Justice, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - United Way Campaign, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - V - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Advisory Council on Substance Abuse, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Association for Children with Learning Disabilities, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Association of Counties, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Association of Elementary School Principals, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Association of Independent Schools, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Association of School Administrators, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Community College System, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Council for the Deaf, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care, Inc., 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Education Association, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Forum on Education, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia High School League, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Municipal League, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Public School Authority, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Register Committee / Registrar of Regulations, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia State Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia State Library, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Virginia Beach, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - W - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Warren County, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Washington County, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Waynesboro, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Westmoreland County, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Williamsburg, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Winchester, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Wise County, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Wythe County, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Y - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Yorktown Bicentennial Committee, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - York County, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - Z - Correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 15a)
    - State Government: Appropriations Committee, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Attorney General, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Attorney General - Civil Digest, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Division of Children, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Comptroller's Office, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Computer Services, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Council of Higher Education, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Employment Commission, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: General Services, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Emergency and Energy Services, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Governor Charles S. Robb - Executive Orders, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Governor's Office, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Virginia Liaison Office, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Copies forwarded, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Education Advisory Block Grant Committee, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Lieutenant Governor, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Administration, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education - Copies forwarded, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education - Memos, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Human Affairs, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Public Safety, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Transportation, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Health Dept., 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Highways Dept., 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Justice and Crime Commission, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Legislative Automated Systems, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Legislative Services, Division of, 1981-1982. (Box 15b)
    - State Government: Management Analysis and System Development, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Miscellaneous state agencies, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Office on Aging, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Rehabilitative School Authority, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: State Agency Auxiliary, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: State agency group luncheon, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Telecommunications, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Transportation Safety, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Treasury Board, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Miscellaneous material, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Certification Update - Association of Teacher Educators, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Cooperating School Personnel - Norfolk State University, 1981 May 1. (Box 16)
    - State Government: Southern Regional Education Board - Taskforce Report on Teacher Certification, 1981 June 29. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Standards of Learning - Priority for the 80s - Virginia Tech, 1981 July 27. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Proposed Budget (1982-1984 Biennium), 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Education Commission of the States panel discussion - Education at the Crossroads: Alternatives for State Leadership, 1981 Aug 27. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Summer school graduation exercises at Hermitage High School, Henrico, VA, 1981 Aug 6. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Virginia Association of School Administrators - Education in the Eighties, 1981 Oct 1. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Dedication of the James Wood High School Ridge Campus, Frederick County, 1981 Oct 11. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Virginia Association for Pupil Transportation, 1981 Oct 12. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Virginia Education Media Association, 1981 Oct 29. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Social Studies Educators - Education for Citizenship, 1981 Nov 6. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Virginia Association of Counselor Educators and Supervisors, 1981 Nov 6. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Conference on Ethics Education, 1981 Nov 12-14. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Tenth Annual Reading Conference, 1981 Nov 20. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Alternative Education Committee - Henrico County Schools, 1980 Dec 2. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Virginia Association of Collegiate Registrars and Admissions Officers, 1981 Dec 6. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Roanoke County Council PTA, 1981 Dec 7. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Nottoway County - Dedication of new middle school, 1981 Dec 13. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1981 Dec 15. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Virginia Municipal League, Seminar for Local Government Officials - Financing Local Government in the Era of Reaganomics, 1981 Dec 17. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Conference for County Supervisors, 1982 Jan 8. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Youth Forum - Great American Achievements / National Bicentennial Debates, 1982 Feb 9. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Henrico County Schools Teacher In-Service meeting, 1982 Feb 22. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Virginia Federal Council for Exceptional Children, 1982 Mar 5. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Performance Evaluation and Provisional Certificate, 1982 Apr 19-20. (Box 16)